hello everybody this is my second song
and the digital campfire series I called
this song Noah's Ark and we're all out
there floating on our own personal arks
with some animals maybe our family and
try to be well so this song is an
admonition this song is saying build
your Ark for the flood waters coming one
two three go
[Music]
are you fine
and the eyes and if you are right
[Music]
human wickedness has no air
just one thing can be done
[Music]
our sires for 300 cubits long and 51
vulnera and a domicile
[Music]
and everything
and your sons your daughters
[Music]
when the floodwaters come
but every creature with
[Music]
[Applause]
I'll make my
[Music]
our star
but I
[Music]
but not a song
she brought
the ark itself
[Music]
[Applause]
the Lord
[Music]
[Applause]